Patthamawan Iteeyaporn (Nune)

INFO

ADDRESS

7 St.Mary Graces Court, Cartwright Street, London, El 8NR

PHONE

07444619169

EMAIL

p.iteeyaporn@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Thai

LINKS

nunefolio.co.uk

SKILLS

Invision, Adobe XD, Figma, Miro

.

Adobe Photoshop

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Adobe Illustrator

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

HTML5/CSS3

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

SASS/LESS

.

React

• 0 0 0 0

Autodesk Maya

• • • • 0

LANGUAGES

English

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Thai

.

HOBBIES

Drawing, Gaming, Movies, Traveling, Playing Piano

PROFILE

I am a UX/UI designer with 4 years of experience. In my most recent role, I was responsible for designing and coding the user interface for all of the company's products. I'm a self-motivated individual, experienced in managing my own workflow and working as part of a team to deliver projects on time.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

UX/UI Designer, Botnoi Consultent

Currently on 6 months contract with Botnoi Consultant.

- · Working closely with CEO to understand the work flow of Chat bot tool.
- · In charge of improving UX / UI design for the Chat bot software tool
- · Using Miro and Figma to plan and design UX / UI.

UX/UI Designer / Web Developer, Zanroo

Apr 2016 — Oct 2019

- Led the design process, managed business expectations and provided regular progress updates.
- Worked closely with the product owners to improve and design new features and products.
- Created prototype and design UX/UI using Sketch, Adobe XD and Invision Studio tools.
- Applied Responsive Web Design when turning UI concept into HTML/CSS using SASS and React framework on the projects.
- · Built a library of reusable components.

Animator, M2 Animation

Aug 2015 — Mar 2016

- · Worked on the 2nd season of Lego's Friends and Lego City mini-movie.
- Pitched ideas on how the scene is going to look to the animation director before animating the scene using Autodesk Maya.
- Helped with cleaning up the animations before the final rendering of the scene

Animator, Kyoraku Pictures

May 2014 — Jul 2015

- Created action sequences for both character and vehicle animation for the Pachinko game machines in Japan.
- · Tested rigs and give feedback to riggers for improvements.
- · Cleanup motion capture using Motionbuilder program.

Junior Animator, Vithita Animation

Oct 2012 — Apr 2014

- Responsible for animating, modelling and texturing everyday objects for a Thai Cartoon TV series.
- Created blend-shapes for characters to achieve believable character movements

EDUCATION

BA(hons) Animation, Staffordshire University

Oct 2008 — Jul 2011